

ALAN FRANCISCO ALVAREZ MALDONADO FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SKILLS

- **★** 00P
- ★ C#
- ★ Visual Basic
- ASP.NET MVC
- Web services, Web Api Rest
- ★ PHP
- JavaScript, JQuery
- **★** HTML
- * CSS
- Bootstrap
- ★ Microsoft SQL Server
- ★ Entity Framework
- ★ MvSOL
- ★ LinQ
- ★ FactoryTalk Transaction Manager
- ★ SAP MII

LANGUAGES

- * Native Spanish
- * Advanced English

COURSES

- ★ C# with ASP.NET Core (2020)
- ★ Asynchronism with JavaScript (2020)
- ★ ECMAScript 6+ (2020)
- ★ JavaScript basics (2020)
- Fronted Developer (2020)
- ★ Good practices and development environment (2020)
- ★ Android development basics (2019)
- ★ Git and Github professional course (2019)
- ★ Bootstrap 4 master (2018)

EDUCATION

Instituto Tecnológico de Estudios Superiores de

Engineering in Information and Communication Technologies | 2011-2016

Centro de Bachillerato Tecnológico Industrial y de Servicios No. 52

IT technician | 2008 - 2011

ABOUT ME

I am a Full Stack Developer passionate about technology, with four years of experience in all software development stages with consideration of customer needs, functionality, the latest technology and programming standards, I've worked for companies in different sectors, contributing to problem-solving and process automation. I'm a fast learner, strong team player with excellent social skills.

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Zamora, Michoacán



April 12, 1993 (27 years old)

github.com/alan1204

in linkedin.com/in/alan-alvarez

WORK EXPERIENCE

Agrana Fruit México

Software development supervisor | September 2018 - March 2020

- Manage web projects.
- Coordination of the software development team.
- Designed, planned, developed, tested and maintained we applications.
- Effectively translated client requirements into application designs and systems requirements.
- Designed, creating and maintaining databases.
- Implemented enhancements that significantly improved web functionality.
- Technical support to users.

Technologies used: C#, Visual Basic, ASP.NET MVC, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, GIT, SQL Server, LinQ, FactoryTalkTransaction Manager, SAP MII.

Software developer | June 2017 - September 2018

- Developed, tested and maintained we applications.
- Technical support to users.
- · Creating and maintaining databases.
- · Fixed bugs from existing websites.
- · Provide effective troubleshooting and remediation for web applications.

Technologies used: C#, Visual Basic, ASP.NET MVC, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, GIT, SQL Server, LinQ.

Servicios y adelantos tecnológicos Proyectall

Web developer | December 2016 - June 2017

- Designed, developed and maintained we applications for different local companies.
- Developed and updating websites and databased for BCP Systems company.

Technologies used: C#, PHP, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, GIT, SQL Server, MySQL

Transportes Castores, León Guanajuato

Programmer analyst | February 2016 - April 2016

· computer systems development to automate the different company departments.

Technologies used: Java, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL.

General Motors of México, Silao Facility

IT department intern | June 2015 - December 2015

· Web system design and development for the administration, monitoring and statistics of failures and findings of the equipment of body shop area.

Technologies used: PHP, JavaScript, JQuery, HTML, CSS, MySQL.

CTS México

Technical support | June 2014 - May 2015

- Technical support to "Little Caesars" in US and Mexico.
- Migrating MySQL databases to SQL Server.
- · Systems upgrade.